Karl M. Waage Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Karl M. Waage Archives
1915-1999
IPAR.001198
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
15
The archives of Karl M. Waage encompassing his career at Yale. These include annotated maps, field notebooks, photographs, correspondence, and biographical material.
Waage, Karl Mensch
Biographical Sketch
Karl M. Waage was born December 15, 1915, in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Influenced early on by an amateur rock and mineral collector, he entered Princeton University in 1935 with an interest in geology. Having been introduced to the geology of the American West by Erling Dorf, Waage?s senior thesis was on the stratigraphy of the Upper Cretaceous Fox Hills Formation in the Lance Creek area of Wyoming.
Waage earned his Ph.D. from Princeton in 1946, with a dissertation on the refractory clays of the Lower Cretaceous Dakota Group of the Colorado Front Range. Hired that year by Yale University, he extended his work on the Dakota Group, clarifying its relationship to the underlying Morrison Formation, drawing attention to the importance of regional unconformities that represented significant time hiatuses, revising its stratigraphy, and providing an interpretation of its depositional environment.
In the mid-1950s, Waage refocused his attention on the Fox Hills Formation in its type area in South Dakota. His enthusiasm for this subject was to mark his research for the rest of his career. His field studies culminated in a 1968 monograph, The Type Fox Hills Formation, Cretaceous (Maestrichtian), South Dakota (Bulletin of the Peabody Museum of Natural History 27), describing the facies relationships, lithologic units, and molluscan zonation. He showed that this formation represented a transition from the environment of a clastic barrier shelf through that of the shoreface of a barrier bar complex during the final retreat of the Late Cretaceous sea.
This work set a standard for paleoenvironmental studies at a time when such studies were first gaining prominence. From the large, well-documented collections amassed during many field seasons, Waage, with his student Neil Landman, produced a monograph on the systematics, life history and distribution of the beautifully preserved scaphited ammonites.
Waage was Director of the Yale Peabody Museum from 1979 through 1982. He and Carl Dunbar wrote a textbook on historical geology, continuing a tradition begun by Charles Schuchert. Retiring in 1986, he wrote several more papers on scaphites and, in 1999, just before his death, co-authored a final manuscript on Holocene fossils from West Haven, Connecticut, a project he had begun 30 years earlier.
Description of the Material
Includes topographic maps (Colorado, Connecticut, New York, North Dakota, South Dakota, Wyoming) and other maps (North Dakota, South Dakota, Utah, Wyoming). Also includes field notebooks (Colorado, Maryland, New Jersey, New Mexico, North Dakota, South Dakota, Utah, Wyoming).
Connecticut; South Dakota; North Dakota; USA; Maps; Photographs; Correspondence; Field notebooks; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Maps, Series I
  - Colorado., 001206
    - Topographic map. Fort Collins, CO 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. Colorado, 1908; 002084
    - Topographic map. Judson Hills, CO 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1967; 002082
  - Connecticut., 001205
    - Topographic map. Woodmont, CT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001947
    - Topographic map. New Haven, CT 7.5 Quad. (1: 31680). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1954; 001946
  - New York., 001204
    - Topographic map. Catskill, NY 15 Quad. (1: 62500) U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1934; 002218
    - Topographic map. Catskill, NY 15 Quad. (1: 62500) U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1934; 002219
    - Topographic map. Kingston East, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1963; 002213
    - Topographic map. Hudson South, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1963; 002214
    - Topographic map. Cementon, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1963; 002216
    - Topographic map. Kingston West, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1964; 002215
    - Topographic map. Rosendale, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1964; 002217
  - North Dakota., 001209
    - Topographic map. Cannon Ball NW, ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1968; 001904
    - Topographic map. Cannon Ball SE, ND 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1968; 002080
    - Topographic map. Strasburg, ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1971; 001893
    - Topographic map. Kiefer Buttes, ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1971; 001905
    - Topographic map. Breien, ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1980; 001902
    - Topographic map. Solen, ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1980; 001903
  - South Dakota., 001210
    - County map. Butte Co (S half) (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1957; 002175
    - County map. Type area of Fox Hills Fm; Locality Key (1: 253440). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1963; 001856
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Wakpala Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1949; 002094
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Pollock Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1951; 002092
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Mahto Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1951; 002098
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Mahto Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1951; 002099
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Mobridge Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1952; 002093
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Isabel Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1952; 002097
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Isabel Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1952; 002191
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Firesteel Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1954; 002095
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Firesteel Creek Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1954; 002187
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Bullhead Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1956; 002096
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the McIntosh Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1957; 002186
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Miscol Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1959; 002189
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Timber Lake Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1960; 002188
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Little Eagle Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1960; 002192
    - Geologic map. Areal Geology of the Glencross Quadrangle, SD 15 Quad (1: 62500). S.D. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1961; 002190
    - Map. Ziebach Co (N half) (1: 62500). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1936; 002162
    - Map. Fall River Co (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1950; 001723
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 1, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001869
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 7, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001872
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 8, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001873
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 10, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001875
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Dewey Co, part 7 (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001878
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Dewey Co, part 11, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001881
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 2, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001883
    - Map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 6, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001887
    - Map. Corson Co (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1957; 001722
    - Map. Meade Co (N half) (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1957; 001724
    - Map. Butte Co (N half) (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1957; 002176
    - Map. Type Area of Fox Hills Fm; Locality Key (1: 253440). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1963; 001728
    - Map. Ziebach Co (1: 258600). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 001727
    - Map. Type area of Fox Hills Fm; Locality Key (1: 487385). Waage, K.M.: County and drainage., 001857
    - Topographic map. State of South Dakota: (1: 500000): Type area of Fox Hills Fm; Locality Key. U.S. Geological Survey; geographic., 1921; 002174
    - Topographic map. Deep Creek NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001678
    - Topographic map. Dupree NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001680
    - Topographic map. Dupree NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001681
    - Topographic map. Faith NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001683
    - Topographic map. La Plant, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001687
    - Topographic map. Promise, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001703
    - Topographic map. Redelm NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001704
    - Topographic map. Redelm NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001706
    - Topographic map. Ridgeview NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001708
    - Topographic map. Ridgeview NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001710
    - Topographic map. Thunder Butte, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001712
    - Topographic map. Trail City SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001714
    - Topographic map. Virginia, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1951; 001716
    - Topographic map. Deep Creek NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001677
    - Topographic map. Deep Creek SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001679
    - Topographic map. Faith NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001684
    - Topographic map. Glencross SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001685
    - Topographic map. Lantry NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001688
    - Topographic map. Lantry NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001690
    - Topographic map. Parade NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001700
    - Topographic map. Whitehorse, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001721
    - Topographic map. Trail City SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1952; 001771
    - Topographic map. Rapid City West, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002085
    - Topographic map. Rapid City East, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002086
    - Topographic map. Tilford, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002088
    - Topographic map. Fort Meade, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002089
    - Topographic map. Hayward, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1954; 002087
    - Topographic map. Sturgis, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1954; 002090
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 2, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001870
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 3, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001871
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Corson Co, part 9, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001874
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Dewey Co, part 2, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001876
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Dewey Co, part 3, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001877
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Dewey Co, part 6, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001879
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Dewey Co, part 5, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001880
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 1, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001882
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 3, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001884
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 4, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001885
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 5, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001886
    - Topographic map. U.S.D.A., Ziebach Co, part 7, SD (1: 20000). U.S. Department of Agriculture: Photomosaic., 1955; 001888
    - Topographic map. Black Horse SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001668
    - Topographic map. Black Horse, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001669
    - Topographic map. Black Horse NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001670
    - Topographic map. Black Horse SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001671
    - Topographic map. Bullhead, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001672
    - Topographic map. Bullhead SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001673
    - Topographic map. Cottonwood Creek NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001674
    - Topographic map. Cottonwood Creek SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001675
    - Topographic map. Cottonwood Creek NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001676
    - Topographic map. Little Eagle, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001692
    - Topographic map. Little Eagle NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001693
    - Topographic map. Little Eagle SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001694
    - Topographic map. Little Eagle SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001695
    - Topographic map. Miscol, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001696
    - Topographic map. Miscol NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001697
    - Topographic map. Miscol SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001698
    - Topographic map. Miscol SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001699
    - Topographic map. Wakpala, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001717
    - Topographic map. Wakpala NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001718
    - Topographic map. Wakpala SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001719
    - Topographic map. Wakpala SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1956; 001720
    - Topographic map. Ziebach Co (N half) (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1958; 001725
    - Topographic map. Ziebach Co (S half) (1: 140800). South Dakota Highway Department: Highway., 1958; 001726
    - Topographic map. Pollock, SD-ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1965; 001908
    - Topographic map. Kenel, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1966; 001894
    - Topographic map. Kline Buttes, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1966; 001895
    - Topographic map. Mahto, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1966; 001896
    - Topographic map. Pollock NW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1966; 001901
    - Topographic map. Mahto NE, SD-ND 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1966; 001907
    - Topographic map. Mobridge NW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1967; 001906
    - Topographic map. Mobridge, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1967; 002079
    - Topographic map. Mc Laughlin SW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1971; 001898
    - Topographic map. Mc Intosh SE, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1972; 001897
    - Topographic map. White Owl 3 NW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Orthophotoquad., 1974; 001863
    - Topographic map. Glencross, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1975; 001748
    - Topographic map. Glencross NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1975; 001749
    - Topographic map. Laundreaux Butte, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1975; 001759
    - Topographic map. Trail City, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1975; 001770
    - Topographic map. Redelm SW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Orthophotoquad., 1975; 001864
    - Topographic map. Bull Creek 2 NW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Orthophotoquad., 1975; 001865
    - Topographic map. Bull Creek 2 NE, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Orthophotoquad., 1975; 001866
    - Topographic map. Bull Creek 2 SE, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Orthophotoquad., 1975; 001867
    - Topographic map. Brewer Butte, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001746
    - Topographic map. Firesteel, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001747
    - Topographic map. Isabel, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001754
    - Topographic map. Isabel SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001755
    - Topographic map. Little Moreau Lake, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001760
    - Topographic map. Livermant Lake, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001761
    - Topographic map. Peach Lake, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001764
    - Topographic map. Timber Lake, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001768
    - Topographic map. Timber Lake, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001769
    - Topographic map. High Elk Hill, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001750
    - Topographic map. High Elk Hill NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001751
    - Topographic map. Herbert Creek, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001752
    - Topographic map. Herbert Creek NE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001753
    - Topographic map. La Plant SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001756
    - Topographic map. Lantry, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001757
    - Topographic map. Lantry SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001758
    - Topographic map. Parade, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001762
    - Topographic map. Parade SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001763
    - Topographic map. Ridgeview, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001765
    - Topographic map. Ridgeview SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001766
    - Topographic map. Rousseau Creek NW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001767
    - Topographic map. High Elk Hill SW, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001910
    - Topographic map. Irish Creek SE, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1982; 001909
    - Topographic map. Red Elm SW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1982; 002074
    - Topographic map. Bessie Butte, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1982; 002076
    - Topographic map. Bull Creek 2 NE, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1982; 002077
    - Topographic map. Red Scaffold, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic, 1982; 002078
    - Topographic map. Marcus, SD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1983; 001922
    - Topographic map. White Owl NW, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1983; 002075
    - Topographic map. Mobridge NE, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1987; 001899
    - Topographic map. Pollock, SD 7.5 Quad (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1987; 001900
    - Diagrams & maps related to Type Fox Hills Fm, South Dakota paper by Waage; YPM Bull 27, 1968; 000773
  - Utah., 001207
    - Map. Location map of fossil localities: Utah., 1947; 000207
  - Wyoming., 001208
    - Highway map. Niobrara County, Sheet 1 of 2 (1: 125000). Wyoming Highway Department: Highway., 1953; 001932
    - Highway map. Niobrara County, Sheet 2 of 2 (1: 125000). Wyoming Highway Department: Highway., 1953; 001933
    - Highway map. Ground Reconnaissance Map of Lance Creek District, WY (1: 20000). Museum of Paleontology, Univ. of Calif., Berkeley: road, 1956; 002073
    - Highway map. Oat Creek, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 001938
    - Highway map. Bowen Flat, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001934
    - Highway map. Buck Creek Hills, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001935
    - Highway map. Telephone Draw, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 001941
    - Locality information. Strawberry Hill, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. [Volume=Preliminary Edition], 1954; 002182
    - Map. Weston Co (1: 281600). Wyoming Highway Department: Highway., 1957; 002091
    - Topographic map. Aladdin, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. [Volume=Preliminary Edition], 1954; 002177
    - Topographic map. Sunny Divide, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. [Volume=Preliminary Edition], 1954; 002178
    - Topographic map. Missouri Buttes, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. [Volume=Preliminary Edition], 1954; 002179
    - Topographic map. Carlile, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. [Volume=Preliminary Edition], 1954; 002180